therealreview.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy – The Real Review

The Real Review operates on the principle that the privacy of its members is paramount. We collect minimal personal information on registration: your email address, a user name, which may but need not be your real name, and your mobile number in case you choose to use it to access the mobile application. That’s it. Even so, it is important that you understand what we do, and do not do, with the information generated through use of The Real Review. Our Privacy Policy contains important information about how we look after your privacy; please read it carefully. We also encourage you to review our Terms and Conditions of Use.

The Real Review reviews its privacy practices from time to time, and may amend this Privacy Policy as required to reflect its business practices, new industry standards or applicable laws or regulations from time to time. We ask that you periodically review this page for updates to our Privacy Policy. To contact The Real Review about privacy issues, to report a violation of our Privacy Policy, or to raise any other issue, please [contact us](https://www.therealreview.com/contact-us/) .

## Personal Information

We do not ourselves store any credit card or payment information. All payments are handled through third-party suppliers. By using them you agree to be bound by their terms of business.

We do not ask you to provide verifiable information relating to your birth date. We do ask you to warrant that you are above the minimum age applicable in the jurisdiction in which you reside for the purchase and consumption of alcohol.

When you use our website, we collect your browser type and IP address and log in information and may store that information using “cookies”. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you use The Real Review again. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience but it will take longer for you to log in to use the website.

You post User Content (as defined in the The Real Review Terms and Conditions of Use) on The Real Review at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Accordingly we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on The Real Review.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on The Real Review is a violation of the The Real Review Terms and Conditions of Use and should be [reported](https://www.therealreview.com/contact-us/).

The Real Review does not provide access to your information to anyone under any circumstances (short of legal compulsion), including third party marketers. Should you wish to deal with third parties who advertise product offerings on or through The Real Review, you must initiate the dealings.

The Real Review collects and aggregates non-personal data to analyse general trends and usage patterns. We provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers, affiliates, and other current and potential business partners. We may also use the aggregate data to inform third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their sites.

The Real Review funds itself through selling advertising through third-party ad servers or ad networks. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may, when you log on to The Real Review, use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear within The Real Review and they automatically receive your IP Address and other log file information when this happens. Such third-party ad servers may also use other technologies (such as cookies) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. The Real Review does not provide your personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks.

## Legal Compulsion

The Real Review may be required to disclose user information under compulsion of law through subpoenas, court orders, warrants or in order to comply with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, and to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through The Real Review.

## Third-Party Web Sites

The Real Review web site contains links to third party sites. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites, including such sites’ use of any data.

Keep in mind that, while The Real Review encourages all third parties involved — such as our affiliates and advertisers, to adhere to our policies regarding our users’ privacy and to otherwise handle personal data in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any acts or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use data received either from The Real Review or independently.

## Changing, Deleting or Deactivating Accounts

Access and control over your personal information on The Real Review is readily available through editing tools. The Real Review users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Individuals who wish to deactivate their account may do so on The Real Review. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not otherwise be generally available to anyone, including the member who has deactivated his or her account.

## Contacting Us

Please [contact us](https://www.therealreview.com/contact-us/) with any questions and comments regarding our Privacy Policy.
